couponcode.com 2019-02-08

# Privacy Statement

LDS Marketing (CouponCode.com®) is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of this site's visitors. To that extent, we are the sole owners of all information collected on this site.

Any information is collected in order to deliver the services you have requested.

This policy applies only to the LDS Marketing web site, and not to other companies' or organizations' web sites to which we link.

LDSM is committed to protecting personal information, by following responsible information handling practices in keeping with privacy laws.

LDSM uses information and communication technologies to support our LDSM activities. Our Privacy Statement covers LDSM and our website.

**Anonymous Access**

You can access our website home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. As a general policy, NO personal information is collected from our visitors. The only personal information captured through our Web site is the information that you volunteer such as your email address or perhaps a mailing address that will enable us to send to you requested information. We do not share any names or email addresses collected during any registration process on this web site with third parties. We do not share, sell, rent, exchange, or give any contact information to anyone.

Safeguards are in place to ensure that the information is not disclosed or shared for any other purposes.

**LDSM's Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identification number that is transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer so that the web site may identify separate visitors to the site and track users' activities on the web site. A cookie will not let a web site know any personally identifiable information about you, such as your real name and address.

We collect information about you only if you volunteer it.

**Newsletter Subscriptions**

When you subscribe to a LDSM Newsletter, you need only supply an email address. This email address is used to deliver the e-mail newsletter to you. Your email is not used or known by any other newsletter subscriber, organization, Web site or government agency.

**Links on our Website**

Because LDSM wants your website experience to be informational and resourceful, our Website also provides a number of links to third party sites.

LDSM assumes no responsibility for the information practices of sites you are able to access through our site. We encourage visitors to review each site's privacy policy before disclosing any personally identifiable information.

**Your Choice**

We collect personal data you volunteer online, or when you make use of or register for our activities and services, in order to better meet your program, service and information needs.

We also use and disclose data, which does not identify individuals, for statistical purposes to develop and enhance LDSM activities and services.

We may also collect personal information in order to satisfy legal, government and regulatory obligations.

If you supply us with your contact information, you may hear from us about important information concerning the LDSM activity or project in which you are involved.

**Information Sharing**

We collect personal information at the user's discretion. This information will be limited to the purpose described to the user when requesting that information. A practical example of a situation like this would be that we may request the user's name and e-mail address in order to send updates of changes to our website or mailing of specific information about our programs. We would not send invitations to events unless the user gives their permission. Similarly, we will not solicit donations using the information received from the user unless the user gives their permission. Permission will not be assumed."

We will collect information for statistical purposes for administration of the website. The stored information will not include any information that reveals any contact information of the user.

**Confidentiality / Security**

LDSM maintains physical, electronic and administrative safeguards that are appropriate to the type of personal information we obtain from you.

LDSM staff and volunteers having access to personal data are required to respect the confidentiality of personal information and handle it responsibly.  

**Privacy Questions**

If you are aware of any inaccuracy or changes in the personal information which we hold about you, please contact an LDSM staff.

If you have a complaint or concern about LDSM's information handling practices, we encourage you to talk to us. You can contact LDSM's Chief Privacy Officer . You will be asked to provide the following information in writing:

Your name, address or fax number where you prefer to be reached;

Nature of your complaint, relevant details, and what you would like us to do;

Name of the LDSM staff with whom you have already discussed the issue.

LDSM will investigate and assist with resolving your concern.

**Ongoing Relevancy**

LDSM regularly reviews its policies and procedures to ensure we remain current with changing laws and evolving public expectations.

LDS Marketing welcomes comments and questions on this policy. Due to the evolving nature of the technologies we use to communicate with you, we may occasionally update this policy. Notice of any revisions will be posted to this site. Any comments or questions regarding our privacy practices, please contact us.
